haniyae.net
U-Umm...
Sensei, what would be the reason you called for me?
Oh, my bad. Well, the truth is...
I wanted to show you this.
Huh?
K-Kou-chan!
The baseball club's ace player and the
team manager's obscenity in the clubroom...
If this gets public,
all of you won't be able to
participate in the summer tournament.
N-No way... When did you...
Aren't you childhood friends?
That's why winning the summer
tournament is a dream of his... Or rather...
...of you two, am I right?
That's too bad!
However, I'm the only one who knows this.
In short, as long as I'll keep my mouth shut...
Th-Then...
Sleep with me, Tachibana.
That's my condition.
Uhh... H-Huh!?
S-Sensei, what are you saying!?
Till Summer Ends Final Volume: Please Don't Look...
I have to tend to Sensei's needs even at my home...
You skip club activities exactly
when your parents are on a trip.
You fail as our club manager, Tachibana.
I'm sorry...
I need to keep fucking you for
this whole day as punishment.
H-How is it?
Does this feel good, sensei?
Yeah, it feels nice...
I can't get enough of this slippery sensation.
Aren't you quite good at this?
Th-Thank you!
Moreover...
Aren't your nipples stiff like nails?
Come on, say it.
Say "I'm a slut who gets off from her nipples"!
Yes! I-I'm...
A slut who gets off from her nipples...
Your voice is too low!
I-I'm a slut who gets off from her nipples!
Yes, that's it.
With this, you'll be able to earn a lot
whoring yourself even if you get expelled.
N-No way...
But I'm...
I'm...
Yes, I'm gonna come!
I'll have today's first shot over
your face... With your tit-pussy!
Yes, please let it out!
S-Shoot plenty onto me...
Please spray lots and lots of it all over me!
Alright!
Hey, what's the matter?
More... Stick out your ass more!
Okay...
But sensei, what are you planning to do?
Since we're already in the bathroom,
I thought that we should use this
chance to clean your ass inside.
No... Don't do that...
It's going in! Stop!
There's so much flowing in!
It's filling up my belly...
That's plenty enough... That should do.
Okay, don't let it leak out.
Ahh! No, don't!
This is yet another excellent tightness to feel!
No! It's gonna leak out if
I don't squeeze it tightly!
I really will end up pooping!
But... But...
When I tighten up my ass, my...
My pussy tightens up too with his cock inside...
And his cock gouges my pussy out so much!
Besides...
Sensei, I'm begging you...
Slow it down...
If this goes on, I... I will come right away!
It'll all gush out if you come right now, won't it?
Yes, forgive me!
I-I can't take this anymore!
I'll plug it up, then.
You can now feel good as much as you want!
A-Ahh! Yes! Right there! Deep inside!
Where is "there"?
In your asshole, or maybe your pussy?
Both of them!
Both your fingers in my ass and
your cock thrusting into my pussy!
They both feel good!
Have an orgasm, then!
Let it out while reaching climax!
Even after sensei went home,
My body won't stop throbbing.
K-Kou-chan...
K-Kou-chan!
I-In your asshole?
Yeah, I want it in my asshole tonight...
Do you think it's weird?
That's not true.
I love you for whatever you are, Yui.
Ahh! Kou-chan!
I like it... I love it!
Your dick feels great!
It feels so good!
Like sensei's...
It's just like sensei's huge cock!
Huh?
S-Sensei?
I-I...
I'm already...
Wow, it's going far inside!
I-It's reaching deep inside my ass!
Ahh, yes! Yes!
But sensei... Why are we
doing it in this room today?
Hey, Tachibana... Try looking outside the window!
Huh?
I-Is that...
Can you see? Your dear
boyfriend is training down there.
N-No!
Everyone is training like mad, but here you are...
Skipping club activities to indulge in sex.
You're a bad club manager.
Th-That's not true!
I'm here because you called
me over for an interview...
Th-That's why...
You mean you're unwillingly doing this
since I'm the one who called you here?
You don't sound convincing when
you're making such a pleased face!
Ahh! No...
Th-That's a lie... You're lying...
I'm not making such a face!
You actually had realized it already, hadn't you?
That you're a nympho who
willingly spreads her legs open!
No... You're wrong!
I... I'm doing this for Kou-chan
as well as everyone's sake...
For everyone's sake?
Then, should we let everyone
see how hard you're working?
No! Don't! Put me down!
Please put me down, sensei!
What are you saying? Here, come on!
Show your asshole taking in my fat
cock and your perverted pussy as well.
Let the baseball club members have a good look!
haniyae.net
Don't do this... Not like this...
Please don't do this... Stop this already... No!
I bet that they'll all be disillusioned
when they learn that their club manager
is making pleased face for their sake!
No way... They'll see me...
Kou-chan and all of the baseball
club members will see how lewd I am...
Is the idea of being seen
by everyone turning you on?
Your asshole started twitching, you know!
No... No, don't say that!
No, this isn't like that...
No, not so rough!
Come, then!
Show them how you have an anal orgasm!
No, I don't want to come!
I don't want to come, and yet...
Don't... Everyone... Don't look, all of you...
I'm begging you!
Everyone, don't look!
Hmm?
Huh? I think I heard Yui's voice just now...
That was the moment I went
beyond the point of no return.
And then, we did it in the
guidance office at one point.
We also did it in the classroom.
There was also a time we did it
home while I'm watching the house.
I'm now like this, thanks to all of that...
Sensei, I'm begging you! More...
Please make me feel more pleasure!
You're eagerly showing your pussy now...
You really turned into a voracious slut!
Alright, then!
It's going in... Sensei's...
Your dick is going inside me!
Sensei! I'm begging you!
More... More... More!
Where does it feel better, in
your pussy or your ass-pussy?
Both of them! It feels good in both of them!
Your cock feels the best!
Well-said! Now that's my living cock sleeve!
I can tell that your whole body is
just like a pussy craving for my cock!
Y-yes, I've been longing
to have your cock inside me!
That's why I'm coming again! I'm gonna come!
My pussy and ass-pussy are
gonna come at the same time!
I'm coming!
Hey, what's this? Your nipple is already this stiff.
Y-Yes...
I'm sorry... B-but...
My nipples are already erect!
My pussy feels good... It
feels good that they got hard!
They became hard!
Sensei, I am a bad club manager... So...
So please punish me!
Y-You can go a bit rougher on me...
Of course, I can come inside you. Right, Tachibana?
Yes! Shoot it out! Please do!
My pussy... Fill my pussy up with a huge creampie!
And then make me come!
Ahh! I-I'm coming again!
Hey, hey... Did you have another orgasm?
How many times does this make now?
The night is still young, you know?
M-My ass... Not my ass...
I'm gonna come again! My ass-pussy feels good!
Hah! You perverted slutty club manager!
That's because...
Sensei... That's because your dick feels too good!
Does that mean my huge package is
better than your boyfriend's peewee?
K-Kou-chan's thing isn't enough for me anymore!
Sensei... It has to be your huge package!
That's good! Now you realize the
fact that you're a living cock-sleeve.
That's...
Wow, it's reaching deep inside!
It's reaching deep inside me!
Your cock keeps getting hot and bigger!
My asshole too...
My nipples as well!
They feel so good!
Sorry... I'm sorry, Kou-chan...
You're the one I love the most,
but I can't go against sensei's dick anymore!
Alright, I'll make you unable to live
without my cock before summer ends!
I'm gonna train you hard, you hear me?
Yes, sensei... Use that cock of yours...
...and train this naughty girl a lot!
You slutty sow! Alright, come.
I'm also going to dump a lot inside you!
How's that? How's that? How's that?
How's that!?
Thank you! I'm coming!
I'm gonna come with you!
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji
haniyae.net